Wait, wait, wait, hold on!
Nogomi, try to calm down.
No, no, no, get it down! Roco! Let's go!
Oh, ma 'am, yes, my prince!
Oh, my prince!
Oh, ma 'am, yes!
Thank you
so
much
for joining us.
I was soux good. I'm sorry.
Baby!
Mead Gura Young!
Hey!
What theCs lower your way 그러면 you, bitch!
I have Team Check 2006 Hey!
I'm Nongong Princessacci
called and then Crabangangang!
Any layman from the programme?
M대eee about toang!
Pushed by the huge I won't
love you! I don't want you!
I don't know!
What?
You're going to buy
another Oinkie Draw ticket?
What a sweet surprise!
Wisdom number one.
Instead of just one person crafting a way.
With two sets of hands
there'll be much more pay.
And that good sir is
the made way I choose.
Oh, paste away, paste away.
Now, wisdom number two.
Um, maybe we should stop, Chief? Why?
Because this song's a total
downer Oh, paste away, paste away.
She's still singing.
So, Chief, how many
more do we have to make?
Each one is a half of a...
So, like a million? A million?
Don't worry, it's fine.
With five of us, it's
only 200,000 per person.
You don't want to give up on
the cafe, do you, Nagomi, huh?
We have to do these now.
If we don't pay the half a million in
interest within the month
for our overdue dues,
they said we have to close shop.
That's right!
The clock's already ticking!
But we're out of ideas.
as our only chance is to move
our fingers at lightning speed!
Just a million more, make these
flowers with all you've got!
The towel has already been rolled!
Ah, you mean dice, not towel.
Hi, Nogomi.
Are those new flyers you have?
They look a little different
from the flyers you had before.
Actually, we can't afford to buy ink,
so we're printing them as light
as possible to get by for now.
uh well that's original
thanks can i ask you something
sure what is it what sort
of things can we do to
bring in money to our
cafe uh let me see i think
special events are always
effective what kind of events
for example we have cosmo
mellows stay tomorrow and
next week it's kofka big
bang having fun events really
helps to bring customers
in wow that actually sounds
like a blast A great idea
is the birthday party.
A birthday? If I recall,
your cafe is part of
the Creatureland group,
so you might be able to ask
another affiliated cafe for help.
Dream big, go, go!
A birthday party? Yes!
Does anyone have a
birthday coming up soon?
Count me out.
I don't want you to know
when my birthday is.
Like, anyone really gets born
around this time of year.
Actually, I turn 36 in two
days. Wow. In two days?
That's too funny.
You have your 36th
birthday coming up, Bronco?
We have no cash.
Use your pig brains instead of money.
Got that, Ronko? Got it. Understood.
I'll help out as well.
Here, have some grub. What?
This crappy slap again?
It's all we have.
Just be glad it has flavor.
Listen, Siobhan, back during the
war, they boiled pumpkin seeds.
Where's the two newbies?
They're planning Ronko's birthday party.
Do you think they'll be ready in time?
If it helps, I came up with
an idea for a flyer. Oh, wow.
Can I take a look?
Oh.
I realize the fact that it lacks impact.
No, it has plenty of that.
I also considered some
potential activities.
I'm not exactly sure where
to insert a coin toss game.
Cointess?
That's way too early for me.
Sure, maybe one day I might be
intrigued, but considering my age...
I don't think age matters
when playing coin toss.
Oh my god!
Anyway, we can't do everything
written on that list!
You really don't think so?
Okay then, let's take a look
and try to consolidate it a bit.
Don't worry, I'll take care of it.
Um, if it might be feasible,
could we get Ronko a birthday
cake or something like that?
A cheap one would do.
Huh?
We're living off stir-fried bean sprouts.
You think we have the
cash for a stupid cake?
But what if Ronko's birthday
party ends up being popular?
Being popular?
Ends up being popular?
Who the heck is gonna come
celebrate Ronko's birthday?
You can do whatever.
Just don't cause any problems
with any of our regulars.
Problems?
I'm the top earner here at Oinky Doink.
Looking after my masters is
what keeps this place going.
Isn't that right, Chief?
Why, of course it is, Lady Yumechi.
Irrelevant maid birthdays should be done
quietly off in the corner somewhere.
Irrelevant?
Hold on, Yumechi.
Shut your mouth, Thunderling!
You two can go off and have
your own party if you want to.
Just keep making flowers.
I told her off good, huh, Lady Yumechi?
But that's not...
Okay, hog heads, time to feed!
That's too funny.
How could they say that?
Ronko?
Could you not sleep, Nagomi?
Sorry.
I couldn't stop thinking about tomorrow.
Have you been working all night?
I figured I should at least get
all of the decorations put up.
Oh, wow.
That's quite impressive.
Can I help at all?
I really appreciate it, but
I'm just about finished here.
Oh, okay then.
What can I do to help
get some reservations?
So you might be able to ask
another affiliated cafe for help.
Dream Big Go Go!
Oh, I know!
Hmm, okay, let's go in.
Wooly fluff!
Welcome home, mistresses.
How may I serve you?
Oh, no need for that.
We're actually from a sister-maid cafe
called the Oinky Doink Cafe. Oh, wow!
A comrade of ours! Oh, yes!
We have an event at 6 o 'clock,
and we were hoping to hand out
some flyers, if that's okay.
Miss Karuko!
Of course, that's fine. Great!
Thank you so much, miss.
Actually, we're a little
short-staffed right now.
If you don't mind, it would be nice if
you could help us out for a little while.
Of course we can.
Right, Ronco?
If my talents will suffice. Suffice?
That's so mature!
It's so lively in here. Yes, it is.
It would be great if
even a small percentage
of these masters stopped
by on their way home.
Excuse me!
We're here visiting from Oinky Doink Cafe.
Please take a flyer.
You're having a birthday party?
Yes, we are.
Ronko here is celebrating
her birthday today.
We're having a party at 6.
It would be great if you could stop by.
Sorry. Is something wrong? Wow.
We have the exact same birthday. What?
Today just so happens to be
my birthday party as well.
I'm so happy I have the same birthday
as such a lovely fellow maid like you.
Holy fluff.
Karuko, happy birthday!
Happy birthday!
Oh no, I didn't realize that.
I'm, uh, I'm so sorry.
How old are you today, Runco?
I'll be turning 36.
You'll be turning 36?
Rat, ox, tiger?
Oh wow, 15 years older than me!
You must have so much experience.
Yikes, is she really a 36-year-old maid?
Talk about ripe.
Oh, did that make you angry?
Not even a little.
I believe that age has nothing
to do with being a cute maid.
Huh?
Oh, I'm sorry.
I didn't hear a word you said.
Let's get out of here, Ronco.
Oh my, leaving already?
Didn't you want to hand
out your party flyers?
These tiny black and white
flyers with super faint ink.
They have originality.
Very muted originality.
They're fine.
I think it's a wonderful
flyer that shows how
passionate Ronco is
about her birthday party.
We should take our leave now.
I'm sorry.
This is all my fault. It's not.
I really appreciated it. What?
Thank you for doing that.
For standing up for me.
Actually, I was really worried?
That you were going to get mad at them!
and go on one of your rampages.
I'm fine.
I don't get angry for my own sake.
Huh?
If I ever get slightly emotional at all,
it's only because someone insults the cafe.
The cafe?
For me personally,
I don't know if I can say that I'm
devoted to the oinky-doink just yet.
The other cafes are so unfriendly.
And honestly, I don't want to
be a part of all this violence.
I know that maids have
to fight, but still.
With turf wars intensifying now,
I don't think it's realistic to
stick with a zero-violence policy.
Ronko, if you intend on
living your life as a maid,
you will need to be prepared
to take up arms at some point.
So you don't like all
the violence, is that it?
It's fine to think that.
If there's one lesson I've learned,
it's what you can stand to lose
if you don't stand and fight.
Please excuse me.
What the?
What business do you have with us?
Filthy pics I made!
You think you can get cocky with us?
Take that!
I thought fighting within the
same group violates our code.
I guess you just really pissed me off.
Won't you come with us
for just a little bit?
We'll leave left.
It's no use!
I can't get out!
Happy birthday, Miss Ronko!
What is the meaning of all this crap?
You just had to have the same
birthday as me, silly pig. Huh?
Same birthday?
In other words, here in Akiba, we don't
need more than one birthday on the same day.
We don't need?
Everyone was so nice.
The other maids who had the same birthday,
well, let's just say they all popped?
and disappeared like pretty red bubbles.
Wait a second.
Are you saying that you killed them all?
Holy fluff.
It's almost time for it to
begin, isn't it? Huh? Your party?
You said it starts at six o 'clock.
Wait!
Oh, don't worry.
I'll host your big
birthday party right here.
It's a special birthday present
Wow, your birthday and the day
that you die are going to match.
Hey, my birthday's on April 2nd!
Lovely, and your point.
That means my birthday won't
match the day that I die.
Oh?
I'm so sorry.
Dream of cute little sheep frolicking
in the night and sleep tight.
Wait, wait, wait, hold on!
Gomi, try to calm down.
No, no, no, I'm gonna drown! Gronko!
Tomato! Gronko!
This is just tomato juice!
That's good news!
What about that is actually good?
Help!
Oh, my!
I put my heart and soul into baking this.
Shining like holy light.
Look at the size of that thing.
Did you really bake this and decorate it?
I did it for her.
Give her a proper celebration.
So we managed to buy a cake?
That's why we lived off of nothing
but bean sprouts, remember?
For better or for worse, there
are still no masters here.
So let's hide this cake fast
and go get ready for the party.
All right.
I'm sure we all thought we were
busted with Yumechi's crabby acting.
Uh, it's hard trying to
act like you're mean.
I'm sure it is.
Anyway, we're going to
have to do our best.
We need to nail Ronco's
birthday surprise, right, Zoya?
Right.
Okay, piggy pranksters,
let's pull this off.
Yeah, that's not it.
All right, we did it.
We made it back up.
Ronco, do you think we're
going to die in here?
At this rate, we will.
You know, Ronco, I always wanted
to live my life as a maid.
Even though I was worried that I
wouldn't have what it takes to be one,
I still got hired.
So tell me, where do you think
it was that I went wrong?
I must apologize.
Huh?
36 years ago today, if I hadn't been
born, we wouldn't be here. Stop that!
Today's an important day for
us to celebrate you being born!
And it isn't right for you to
put yourself down like that.
I don't deserve such kind words.
You see, Nogome, I was rolling
in the joint up until last year.
So the only thing to look
forward to was a single donut
in Café au lait that was
given to me for my birthday.
Rolling in the joint? Yes.
I was locked up.
That's why I was looking forward
to my birthday this year.
Oh, joint!
That kind of joint!
Yeah, the pin.
Oh, well then, I respect
you for the time you served.
I'm sorry, this is all my fault.
No, on the contrary.
You have my gratitude
because planning my birthday
party with you was a
very happy time for me.
Circumstances brought me to the cafe,
but I am grateful that I got to
join Oinky Doink as a cute maid.
Ronco, I'm sorry.
No, not to worry.
The others should be out
searching for us very soon.
They'll never find us.
Good evening.
I'm Ronko Manon.
They're late!
Where the heck are those hog heads?
They're wasting our time!
What's the big idea of being
late to their own party?
If they never come back here,
that'll be way too funny.
Then Ronko's cake will be for nothing.
Of course that wouldn't dare
happen. Yeah, like hell.
No way I'd let that fly.
That's them.
Uh, I'm confused.
Hey, did you see Nogomi and Ronko? Huh?
What's this?
Looks like we need to buy more ink.
Thank you so much.
Thank you, Lily Flop.
So heavy.
Nogomi, hold your mouth up higher.
I'm trying.
I'm going to have to.
What are you doing?
I'll drink it all down. For real?
That's impossible.
Bronco, I have to confess.
I lied earlier.
Actually, I'm glad I got to be a maid
that I got to doink-oink-y-doink.
Nogami! Nogami!
Miss Cowrako, we apparently broke
a revenue record today. Of course.
It was my birthday party after all. I...
Are you out of your minds?
We're affiliated.
Like we care!
There's a surprise birthday
party at stake here!
Who are you?
Yo, Lamb Chop!
We don't have the money to buy ink!
Huh?
Bring us Rocco and
Nagomi right now, dammit!
You want our cake to go to waste?
Stupid smelly porkers.
Sounds like you want to
be turned into bacon.
Can it, bitch!
We're pissed and super hungry!
I won't let our days of eating
beansprouts be for nothing!
I'm holding all you mutton accountable.
We'll show you exactly what happens.
When you take us paper-wagly!
Hello, Tomatoes.
Would you like to play with me?
Aw, you're super cute!
What the...?
Nogomi! Nogomi!
We're gonna get you out of here, man.
You cost us a major hassle.
We're getting out of here now
I'm so sorry
Nagomi are you all right? Nagomi!
So like what are we
gonna do with this mess?
Why the hell should I care
about this crappy place?
They should have known
they had it coming to them.
You worthless sowas.
You're finished.
There's no way the Creatureland
group will let this slide.
This is the end of your cafe.
Die in the gutter, filthy pigs!
Are you kidding me?
You wooly bitches kidnapped the
two of them in the first place.
Between me and that maid?
Which one of us do you think offers
more value to the Creatureland group?
What?
I'm saying that shabby old
bag doesn't cut it as a maid.
She's a joke to the profession.
I'm the one the group
needs in their flock.
Not that shitty maid who can't
hope to bring in customers!
How's that for shabby?
There are no shitty
maids. Not in our cafe.
Happy birthday to you.
I hope you enjoyed it.
A maid missing out on her own
party that's unbelievable!
I'm so very sorry.
No, I should be the one.
If you want to apologize,
say it to the chief first.
She ended up managing the
whole thing by herself.
Go ahead.
You two go inside first. Okay.
If you say so.
Uh.
Why are the lights off?
Happy birthday to you!
Happy birthday, dear Rongo!
Happy 36th birthday!
Hey, piglets!
Why are you crying? To go me.
Oh, I'm not crying.
The cake is smaller. What?
Yo, dipshit.
No, you've got it all wrong.
You've ended up ate it.
Pull that piece of cake out of your...
I can't do it.
Today, for the first time,
I found that there are
people in this town?
who I truly cherish.
Sparkly cute to the prime, come to me on
sublime, super duper showtime, understand?
Take a seat and listen
to my Cinderella story.
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
Here's how to become a lady with charm.
Look in the mirror, chant a spell.
You have to be smart and elegant too.
Really, I'm completely different.
What to do?
Oh, romance and dreams.
I want it all I don't have the time to be
feeling down because I'm made to be a girl
Which means be caring be daring and be
preserving or whatever to
have the happiest life.
It's a non-stop mad dash
No, I don't want to know where this
came from what goes around comes around,
you know I got you not you So it's fine.
You're okay with this
You're such a great panda!
You could be in a zoo!
You would be adored by millions!
How about the main
attraction at a petting zoo?
Wouldn't that be great?
Those are the proceeds from MaidShip.
MaidShip?
Yeah, sorry.
We went and wiped MaidShip completely out.
So exciting, what a thrill!
Everyday busy, oh my god!
So much sparkle, heart and glow!
Inside I feel seventeen!
So exciting, what a thrill!
Sorry for the trouble, all in fun!
So much sparkle, heart and glow!
Dore it all with a pretty heart!
Love me too!